能见度，一。
Visibility, one.
天花板4000 多云。温度……萨拉赫1-1-4可以降落，跑道1-1。
Ceiling 4,000 overcast. Temperature... Salah 1-1-4 clear to land, runway 1-1.
可以降落萨拉赫1-1-4。
Clear to land Salah 1-1-4.
这些街道，它们是不同的。
These streets, they're different.
他们老了。
They're old.
这种联系是深厚而隐蔽的。
The ties are deep and hidden.
这是东方钳制西方的地方。
It's where the East claws at the West.
南方寻找北方的地方。
Where the South seeks the North.
这里有必须尊重的荣誉。
There's honor here that must be respected.
不能被打破的规则。
Rules that cannot be broken.
如果犯了错误……
And if a mistake is made...
…没有地方可以躲。
...there's nowhere to hide.
房间服务。
Room service.
浪人一号，我是克利奥帕特拉。
Ronin 1, Cleopatra here.
浪人一号，收到。
Ronin 1, copy.
克利奥帕特拉,走了。
Cleopatra, go.
我在守望先锋。
I'm on overwatch.
关闭引擎。
Shutting down engines.
浪人1号，出租车到了。站在。
Ronin 1, taxi has arrived. Stand by.
浪人1号，待命。
Ronin 1, standing by.
浪人1号，开门！门!
Ronin 1, doors! Doors!
-浪人一号，收到。-司机门。
- Ronin 1, copy. - Chauffeur doors.
司机来开门！
Chauffeur on doors!
浪人五号准备出发。
Ronin Five ready to go.
收到，浪人五号，待命。
Copy that Ronin Five, stand by.
浪人一号，加油！去开!
Ronin One, go karat! Go karat!
罗宁收到一份，开始。
Ronin One copy, go go.
嘿!有什么问题吗？
Hey! What's the problem?
道歉!有人报警说有炸弹。
Apologies! Someone called in a bomb threat.
这里是禁区！
This is a restricted area!
-跪下！-跪下！
- Get on your knees! - Get on your knees!
跪下！把手举起来！
On your knees! Show me your hands!
-跪下！
- On your knees!
给我他妈的跪下，马上！
Get on your fucking knees, right now!
-躺下！躺下!-趴下！
- Lay down! Lay down! - Lay fucking down!
躺下!马上躺下。不要动!
Lay down! Lay down right now. Don't move!
不要动!我吧!
Don't move! On me!
-手，手！-把手举起来！
- Hands, hands! - Show me your hands!
你，出来！出来!你，出来。趴在地上！
You, come out! Come out! You, come out. On the ground!
下来!
Get down!
很明显!
It's clear!
三角洲2号，三角洲2号，请检查4号机库。
Delta 2, Delta 2, please check hangar 4.
我的屏幕是空的。
My screen is empty.
我不知道这是怎么回事。完毕。
I don't know what's going on there. Over.
收到，我这就去。
Copy, on my way.
小队前往4号机库。
Unit en route to hangar 4.
狗嗅出了气味。
Dogs on the scent.
浪人一号，计时！该走了！
Ronin One, clock! Time to go!
-包在手。-包在手。退出。
- Package in hand. - Package in hand. Exiting.
-我们走吧！-我们走吧！我们走吧!
- Let's go! - Let's go! Let's go!
不坏!
Not bad!
移动。
Moving.
-克利奥帕特拉，浪人一号。-轮胎滚动。轮胎滚动。
- Cleopatra, Ronin One. - Tires rolling. Tires rolling.
-如果他抓到我们…快点，快点！
- If he catches us... - Faster, faster!
两个小队离开四号货仓。
Two units leaving Cargo 4.
找出这两个单位。
Identify both units.
司机，我是浪人一号。
Chauffeur, this is Ronin One.
门!门!
Doors! Doors!
我们好吗?
We good?
我们清洁。我们清洁。还好。
We clean. We clean. Still good.
克利奥帕特拉，我们安全了，正在行动。
Cleopatra, we are clear and on the move.
昨晚在比利时，萨拉赫航空公司的1-1-4航班，也就是飞往非洲的航班，钻石行业成为了一场精心策划的抢劫的中心
In Belgium last night, Salah Airline flight 1-1-4, that was the Africa flight, with the diamond industry became the epicenter of a meticulously executed heist
在安特卫普国际机场货运站。
at the Antwerp International Airport cargo terminal.
事件发生时，这架从约翰内斯堡起飞的飞机刚刚抵达机场，身穿警察战术装备的嫌疑人冲过停机坪，对货机库发动了袭击。
The incident unfolded as the flight arrived from Johannesburg, and suspects in police tactical gear raced across the tarmac to stage an assault on the cargo hangar.
初步报告显示，窃贼偷走了价值数百万美元的钻石。
Preliminary reports suggest that the thieves made away with millions of dollars' worth of diamonds.
有迹象表明黑豹黑手党可能是这次精心策划的抢劫的幕后主使。
Indications point to the Panther mafia as potential orchestrators behind this meticulously planned robbery.
继续走，你来对地方了。
Keep on walking, you're in the right place.
后座。
Backseat.
我相信你知道怎么用。
I trust you know how to use it.
格洛克。
Glock.
不安全。
No safety.
我的身份是什么？
So, what's my cover?
你是科特迪瓦血统的法国人。
You're French of Cote d'Ivoire descent.
你是在伦敦工作的钻石商，我们是EDM俱乐部的推广人员来为接下来两周的音乐节做宣传。这就是我们的时钟。
You're a diamond dealer working out of London, and we're EDM club promoters here to promote the festival for the next two weeks. So, that's our clock.
希望你给我找了个好视野。
Hope you got me a good view.
我们今天下午会见销赃人。
We'll meet the fence this afternoon.
她是看客，她为你安排了办公室。
She's a sightholder and she arranged office space for you.
我们已经对整个公寓进行了消毒。
And we've sanitized the whole flat.
所以，你可以走了。欢迎来到尼斯，让-雅克。
So, you're good to go. Welcome to Nice, Jean-Jacques.
开始吧。
Here we go.
让-雅克•Dyallo。
Jean-Jacques Dyallo.
-你他妈在干什么？-跟着他。
- What the fuck are you doing? - Follow him.
跟着那辆该死的车。
Follow that fucking car.
我们在做什么？
What are we doing?
只是放松。你会没事的。
Just relax. You're gonna be fine.
出去。
Get out.
一个不抽烟的脱衣舞女。
A stripper that doesn't smoke.
这是第一次。
That's a first.
去你妈的。
Go fuck yourself.
还在夜店卖劣质食物吗？
Still dealing bad food at the club?
好吧。你的哥们把一切都告诉你了。
Okay. Your dude told you everything.
总是这样。
Always do.
你知道美联储。
You knew about the Fed.
你总是干你的嫌疑犯？
You always fuck your suspects?
这是警察的程序吗？
Is that police procedure?
我可以关上这些集装箱的门，然后运往中国。
You know, I could close these container doors, and then it'll be shipped to China.
当它到达那里时，他们会打开门，你就在那里了。
And when it gets there, they'll open the doors and there you'll be.
死了。
Dead.
一个死在中国的脱衣舞娘。
A dead stripper in China.
听起来变态。
Sounds kinky.
不，没有。
No, it doesn't.
我们简单点说。
We'll make this simple.
既然梅里曼死了，你得告诉我两件事。
Since Merrimen's dead, you're gonna tell me two things.
他和唐尼去了什么没去的地方？
Where were he and Donnie going that they didn't get to?
他们用这些钱做了什么？
And what did they do with the money?
谁是那个幸运的家伙？
Who's the lucky guy?
他一副监狱里的样子。
He was all prison weird.
他没有操我。
He didn't fuck me.
你所做的。
You did.
我可以发布这个…任何时候。
And I can post this... anytime.
神。我看起来年轻多了。
God. I look so much younger there.
我知道唐尼去哪了。
I know where Donnie went.
我知道他把钱放在哪里了。但我要我男人的那份。
I know where he put the money. But I want my man's cut.
七百万年。
Seven million.
不然洛杉矶警局和你的女儿们会为你的业余色情事业感到无比骄傲。
Or the LASD and your daughters will be super proud of your amateur porn career.
你明白吗，混蛋？
You understand, motherfucker?
钱在哪里？
Where is the money?
尼斯钻石银行。
The Nice Diamant Bank.
嘿。
Hey.
让-雅克，这是我可爱的朋友哈瓦。
Jean-Jacques, this is my lovely friend Chava.
那么，我知道你是法国人？
So, I understand you are French?
我们可以说法语吗？
May we speak in French?
我有法国护照。我有点... ...生疏了。
I have a French passport... I am a bit... ...rusty.
干这行你得说英语，所以…你是在阿比让长大的还是…——Tengrela。——哦!
Well, you have to speak English in this business anyway, so... You grow up in Abidjan or... - Tengrela. - Oh!
所以，你是鲍勒族。
So, you're Baoule, ethnically.
种族吗?辛弗拉城。
Ethnically? Sinfra.
给我留下了深刻的印象。
I'm impressed.
你对这个国家很了解。
You know a lot about the country.
我的意思是，我有很多朋友在这一行来自西非。
I mean, I have a lot of friends in this business from West Africa.
艰难的谈判。
Tough negotiators.
谁不是呢?
Who isn't?
让-雅克，你有什么东西想让我看看吗？
So, Jean-Jacques, you have something you want me to look at?
我做的事情。
I do.
-你偶然发现了这个…——我的家人。
-And you came across this... -My family.
我们在博茨瓦纳做生意。
We do business in Botswana.
继续。
Go on.
好了。
Great.
我不打扰你们了。
I'll leave you guys to it.
我帮你在证券交易所安顿好。
Let's get you set up at the Bourse.
-再见。-再见。
- Good day. - Good day.
请出示您的证件。
May I see your identification, please.
啊哈。
Uh-huh.
夹克。
The jacket.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
先生。
Monsieur.
-你好。-你好。
- Bonjour. - Bonjour.
你好。
Bonjour.
新人... ...穿过证券交易所。
The new guy... ... walking through the Bourse.
是吧。
D'accord.
盯紧他，好吗？
Keep an eye on him, yeah?
是的。
Oui.
精彩。请给我一点时间。
Wonderful. Just give me a moment, please.
-谢谢。你可以走了。-谢谢。
-Thank you. You are good to go. -Thank you.
-你好,Chava !你好吗？-你好!
-Hi, Chava! How are you? -Hello!
让-雅克·迪亚洛，这是前台的奥利维尔。
Jean-Jacques Dyallo, meet Olivier, the Concierge.
欢迎光临!
Welcome!
给你。
Here you are.
我可以看看你们的存货清单吗？
May I see your inventory?
你可能。
You may.
正确的。很好。
Right. Very good.
给你，Dyallo先生。你的办公室。
Here you are, Mr. Dyallo. Your office.
-你的办公室。-这里有座机。
- Your office. - Landline phone here.
拨3是保安，7是礼宾部，8是拨出去。
Dial 3 for security, 7 for the Concierge, and 8 to dial out.
你的安全。
Your safe.
你在这里输入你自己的个人代码。
You dial in your own personal code here.
但说实话，你可以让它敞开着。
But you could leave it open, to be honest.
你在欧洲大陆最安全的大楼里。
You're in the most secure building in continental Europe.
我当然希望如此。
I certainly hope so.
这周我有一些存货要来。
I have some inventory coming in this week.
能不能租一个保险箱？
Is it possible to lease one of the vault boxes?
哦，对不起，不可能。
Oh, I'm sorry, not possible.
目前，所有保险库的箱子都订满了。
Currently, all the vault boxes are fully booked.
而且它们都是留给旁观者的。
And they are reserved for sightholders anyway.
啊!
Ah!
希望会有转机。
Hopefully, something opens up.
-再见。-再见。
- Good day. - Good day.
所以呢?
So?
我们在。但是我们有一个问题。
We're in. But we have a problem.
没有进入金库的通道。
There's no access to the vault.
只有达利的持枪者才能进入，而且没有安全箱可用。
Only sightholders in Dali have access, and there's no security boxes available.
你他妈的在跟我开玩笑吧。
You've gotta be fucking kidding me.
让我来处理吧。
Just let me handle it.
赞助人，很抱歉，我有件事要和你商量。
Patron, I'm sorry but there's something I need to discuss with you.
你又要把我挪走？
You have to move me again?
请坐。
Have a seat.
你投资的那块石头。它被偷了。
The stone you invested in. It was stolen.
窃贼抢劫了运送它的飞机。
Thieves robbed the airplane that was transporting it.
它现在在尼斯，靠近钻石中心…有人把它卖出去了。
It's now in Nice, near the diamond center... Someone is fencing it.
找到它。
Find it.
- 3274克拉。-质量上乘。
- 3274 karats. - Excellent quality.
那30k的呢？
What about the 30 karat?
嗯,嗯…这真是一件艺术品。
Well, well... This is really a work of art.
GPS信标。
GPS beacon.
有人在找这个。
Someone's looking for this.
我可以吗?
May I?
提供5.2。如果进展很快，起飞45分钟。
Offer 5.2. If it goes quickly, take off 45.
如果是现金，起飞55。
If it's in cash, take off 55.
粗糙的那个呢？
What about the rough one?
包括一切。
3.87 including everything.
你在街对面有个账户吗？
You have an account across the street?
当然。报价是多少？
Of course. What is the offer?
这些宝石显然没有金伯利证书。
Well, these stones obviously don't come with Kimberley certificates.
4.2.
我…我不能低于5。
I... I cannot go lower than five.
这也是你能得到的唯一机会，让-雅克。
It is also the only offer you will get, Jean-Jacques.
好的!我们做完了！
Ok! We are done!
- 4.2。-这是您的现金。
- 4.2. - Here's your cash.
我知道我们有一个玛萨拉。
I understand we have a Marsala.
我们换成英语吧，这样大家都能听懂。
We'll switch to English so everyone will understand.
好吧。
All right.
通讯是安全的，所以我们可以畅所欲言。——好的。
Comms are secure, - so we can speak freely. - Okay.
我是克利奥帕特拉。
I am Cleopatra.
我和你们每个人都单独合作过，但从来没有合作过。
Now, I've been working with each one of you individually, but never as a group.
你们都来这里是有原因的。
There's a reason why you're all here.
这将是我们在非洲大陆最大的工作。
This will be our biggest job on the continent yet.
这不是打砸抢。
This isn't a smash and grab.
我们是来抢劫世界钻石中心的。
We're here to rob the World Diamond Centre.
我们估计损失为8.5亿欧元。
We estimate the score to be 850 million euros.
使用这些sim卡，并且只使用这些sim卡进行所有通信。
Use these SIMs and only these for all communication.
笔电、物流。马尔科，车辆和运输。
Vuk, logistics. Marko, vehicles and transport.
德拉甘，保险箱，进入。斯拉科夫，通讯，监守所。
Dragan, safes, entry. Slavko, comms, cell overwatch.
-这家伙是谁？——雅克。
- Who is this guy? - Jean-Jacques.
他会负责侦察和策划。
He'll be doing the recce and the planning.
他在这里做什么？
What the fuck is he doing here?
这是我的工作。
This is my job.
我付账单。
And I pay the bills.
这就是我正在做的。
That's what the fuck I'm doing.
-好了，好了，伙计们。-冷静点，好吗？
- Okay, okay, guys. - Calm the fuck down, okay?
这家伙是世界上最厉害的小偷之一？
This guy is one of the best thieves on the planet, okay?
你他妈的有什么毛病？
What the fuck is your problem?
你疯了吗，带他来这儿？
Are you out of your mind bringing him here?
-是啊，这很正常。——等等!嘿，闭嘴！
- Yeah, it's fucking normal. - Wait! Hey, shut the fuck up!
——好的。我们必须在这个月的最后一个星期天之前完成这项工作。
- Okay. - We have until the last Sunday of the month to execute the job.
所以，在我们向目标前进的过程中，世界钻石中心，收集我们需要的情报会很困难。
So, as we advance in our recce to the target here, the World Diamond Centre, gathering all the intelligence we need will be difficult.
让·雅克是我们在内部的线人。
Jean-Jacques is our asset on the inside.
他找到了通往金库的路。
He finds our path to the vault.
如果你对此有意见，你现在就给我滚。
And if you have a problem with that, you can get the fuck out now.
我很好，老板。
I'm good, boss.
你需要什么？
What do you need?
我需要所有安全系统的品牌，品牌和型号，当然还有金库。
I'll need brands, makes and model of all security systems, and of course, the vault.
需要确认他们所有人员的身份。
Need to ID all their personnel.
了解我们在和谁打交道，然后以某种方式窃听他们的通讯。
Get to know who we are dealing with, and somehow, tap in their comms.
确认路线，找到出口。
Confirm routes, find the exits.
我来研究一下路线。在选择车辆之前，我需要先看看他们。
I'll work up the routes. I'll need to see them before selecting vehicles.
-好了吗？-是的。
-So, are we good? -Yeah.
啊,布拉沃。
Ah, bravo.
-做好你的本职工作。-你怎么了？
- Just do your job. - What's with you?
-别废话了。他妈的!
-And cut the crap. -Fuck this!
开始吧。
Here we go.
法国。意大利。
France. Italy.
那个弯道，就是边界。
That bend, that is the border.
这是高山赛跑。
This is the alpine run.
这些路上没有闭路电视或车牌阅读器吗？
No CCTV or plate readers up on these roads?
零。都在海岸上。
Zero. All on the coast.
这就是路线。
This is the route.
我需要全轮驱动。
I need all-wheel drive.
去掉自动化。没有防抱死。
Strip out the automation. No anti-locks.
他还想让我给他口交？
He wants me to suck his dick too?
不好意思，那是什么？
I'm sorry, what was that?
先生，是的，先生。
Sir, yes, sir.
打扰一下。
Excuse me.
对不起。
Sorry.
船长在吗？Capitaine吗?
Is the captain here? Capitaine?
哦，对，对。
Uh, oui, oui.
-没问题。-好吧。
- No problem. - Oh, okay.
我们约在下午一点，一点。
We were set for, uh, 1:00, 1:00 p.m.
这是……这是……这是1:30。
It's... it's... it's 1:30.
他知道我在这里或者…尼古拉斯。雨果。
He's aware that I'm here or... Nicholas. Hugo.
受欢迎的。
Welcome.
很高兴终于见到你了。我以为我们说的是1点，但是…否。
Nice to finally meet you. I thought we said 1:00, but... No.
嗯。
Hmm.
不管怎样，我给你带了点东西。
Well, anyway, I brought you some swag.
我想你和大家可能会喜欢。
Thought you and the guys might like it.
哦。
Oh.
谢谢你，我的朋友，太好了。
Thank you my friend, that's great.
我有LAPD，但没有LASD。很酷。
I have LAPD but not LASD. It's cool.
你想吃点什么，喝点什么吗？
Do you want something to eat, drink?
咖啡。来点牛角面包吧。
Coffee. Maybe a little one of those croissants.
不,尼克。
No, Nick.
这是羊角面包，不是牛角面包。
It's croissant, not, uh, croissant.
很明显，我不会说法语，对吧？
Well, clearly, I don't speak French, right?
美国人是怎么做的？
What American does?
我是瓦拉内中尉。中尉奥布莱恩。
This is Lieutenant Varane. Lieutenant O'Brien.
嘿，很高兴见到你。
Hey, nice to meet you.
一杯咖啡和一个羊角面包。
A coffee and a croissant.
切丽!
Cherie!
请给我一杯咖啡和一个羊角面包好吗？
Could you bring me a coffee and a croissant, please?
啊。
Ah.
所以，它们在这里。
So, here they are.
啊,是的。
Ah, oui.
它很难破解。种族孤立。
It's very tough to crack. Ethnically insular.
他们偶尔会和意大利人和阿尔巴尼亚人合作，但在战术上，他们是聪明的。
They work with the Italians and Albanians once in a while, but tactically, they are brilliant.
玩家只知道谁在牢房里做一项特定的工作。
The players are only aware of who's in the cell for a particular job.
所以，如果他们被抓了，就没人告发了。
So, if they get caught, there's no one to rat on.
是。
Yes.
而且很难识别。
And tough to ID them.
我们没有从巴尔干走廊得到多少帮助。
We don't get much help from Balkan Alley.
他们都像安全部门和军队。
They are all like security services and military.
他们知道如何隐藏自己。
They know how to stay off the grid.
他们经常使用那些在西欧生活了很长时间的模特或运动员。
They often use women who were models or athletes who spend a lot of time in Western Europe.
所以，他们有联系。熟悉周围的环境。
So, they have connections. Know their way around.
这个家伙。斯洛博丹·。
This guy. Slobodan.
他是个罪犯。
He's a criminal receiver.
他和Ndrangheta以及意大利所有顶级珠宝商都有交易。
He has deals with the 'Ndrangheta and all the top jewelers in Italy.
他对欧洲大陆上的每一项工作都开了绿灯。
He gives the green light for every job on the continent.
我们花了将近十年的时间想要抓住他。
We've been trying to bag him for almost a decade.
请坐，尼克。
Take a seat, Nick.
跟我们说说你的嫌疑人吧。
So, tell us about your suspect.
我们有理由相信……谢谢你！
We have reason to believe... Thank you.
…他在欧洲以外活动，可能是法国
...that he's operating out of Europe, possibly France.
我们在安特卫普比赛后开始调查。
We started looking into it after the Antwerp rip.
那件案子的很多签名都和我们在洛杉矶调查过的一些很相似
A lot of the signatures of that job were similar to some of the ones we investigated in L.A.
但是你知道，航空警察认为他们中的大多数是巴尔干人。
But you know, the Police Aeronautique believe that most of them were Balkan.
你不是说除了一个都是巴尔干半岛的吗。
I thought you said that they were all Balkan except for one.
招募他们的人。
The one who recruited them.
好吧。他是布莱克吗？
Okay. And was he Black?
是。
Yes.
——好的。-所以，重点是他们不都是巴尔干人。
- Okay. - So, they weren't all Balkan is the point.
否。
No.
你们能调出我要的监控录像吗？
Were you guys able to pull up the surveillance footage I requested?
当然
Of course.
好吧。
Okay.
我能看看吗？
Can I see it?
你的牛角面包怎么样？
How's your croissant?
好了。
Great.
你在这里的时候我会让你的生活轻松一点。
I'll make your life a little bit easier while you're over here.
你知道，有些法语字母是不发音的。
You know, some of the letters in French, they are silent.
比如牛角面包里的“T”。
Like the "T" in croissant, for example.
你知道，在美国，你说鲑鱼，对吧？
You know, in American, you say salmon, right?
但是“L”是不发音的，不是吗？
But the "L" is silent, no?
我被偷拍了吗？
Am I on Candid Camera or something?
其实我说的是三文鱼。总是有。
You know, I actually say salmon. Always have.
——Sal-mon。好了，就是这样。
- Sal-mon. So, there you go.
他是个有趣的人，对吧？
He's a funny guy, huh?
好吧。这是你要求的那天留下的。
Okay. This is from the day you requested.
让我知道什么时候暂停。
Let me know when to pause.
就是这样。钻石银行。
That's it. Diamant Bank.
等等，等等，停下。在这里。你能放大吗？
Wait, wait, wait, stop. Right there. Can you zoom in?
他出来的时候尽量找他。
Try and find him when he comes out.
好吧,只是……停止。
Okay, just... Stop.
好吧。英寸。
Okay. Inch forward.
别动。别动。
Freeze. Freeze there.
进去。
Go in.
那么,这他吗?
Alors,this him?
不,不。不,不。不是他。
No, no. No, no. Not him.
没有?
No?
否。
No.
如果你还需要什么，有我的电话号码。
If you need anything else, you have my number.
也许我们可以出去吃点鲑鱼。
Maybe we can go out and have some salmon.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
-法国菜有点难吃。-哦。
-French food kinda sucks. -Oh.
事实上，尼克，这是最好的。
Actually, Nick, it's the best.
但是你们美国人，你们没有品味。
But you American, you have no taste.
我是。
I am.
美人计已设。检查你的飞马。
Honey trap is set. Check your Pegasus.
我们知道了。
We got it.
小姐。
Mademoiselle.
找个座位坐下。
Grab a seat.
来吧，老兄，坐下。你让我很紧张。
Come on, man, sit down. You're making me nervous.
我不会咬人的。的承诺。
I won't bite. Promise.
你在打包什么？
So, what you packing there?
你在这里没有管辖权。
You don't have any jurisdiction here.
——Mm !
--Mm!
我没有抢劫美联储。
I didn't rob the Fed.
谁说美联储了？
Who said anything about the Fed?
你知道我刚才被什么绊倒了吗？
You know what I was tripping on just now?
你和我是这个奇怪的共生关系的一部分。
You and I are part of this weird symbiosis.
瞧，小姐，你的存在完全是因为我。
See, you only exist, Fraulein, because of me.
我们不是去阻止你走私和偷东西，那你的东西就一文不值了。
We weren't there trying to stop you from smuggling shit and stealing shit, then your shit wouldn't be worth a fucking thing.
这么麻烦是值得的，因为我们是来阻止你的。
It's only worth the trouble, because we're there trying to stop you.
所以，实际上，你需要感谢我…
So, actually, you need to thank me...
你的东西还值多少钱。
that your shit is worth anything at all.
你是受欢迎的。-好的。
-You're welcome. -Okay.
当有人拿枪指着别人的时候，我就笑。
Cracks me up when people pull guns on people.
-你为什么不直接毙了他们？
- Why don't you just shoot 'em?
你不是杀手。我是。
You're not a killer. I am.
你骗了我，小姐。没人能骗过我。
You got over on me, Fraulein. No one gets over on me.
我破产了。
I'm broke.
我受够了当猎人了。
And I'm sick of being the hunter.
真他妈累人。
It's fucking exhausting.
让我们看看你的观点。
Let's take a look at your view.
洛杉矶街头都在传你被炒了。
Word around the L.A. streets is that they fired your ass.
那你要怎么进去？
So, how you gonna get in?
把它。
Take it.
我再问你一次。
I'm gonna ask you again.
你要怎么进去？
How are you gonna get in there?
我正在努力。
I'm working on it.
不，你不能相信我。
No, you can't trust me.
我随时都可以把你拖进去。
And yeah, I can haul your ass in anytime I want.
取决于我的心情。
Depends on my mood.
小姐，现在一切都很好。
Right now, Fraulein, it's pretty good.
你会抢那个地方的。我要和你一起做。
You're gonna rob that place. And I'm gonna do it with you.
我想见见这些黑豹。
I wanna meet these Panthers.
设置它。
Set it up.
他妈的。
Fuck.
你好,老板。
Hello, boss.
这地方的食物怎么样？
How's the food in this fucking place?
没关系。没什么特别的。
It's okay. Nothing special.
新式烹饪，我的天。
Nouvelle cuisine my ass.
Patron很生气。
Patron is pissed.
他一半的退休金都投资在那颗钻石上了。
Was half his damn retirement invested in that diamond.
他他妈就是章鱼，所以我们最好找到它。
And he's the fucking Octopus so we better find it.
我喜欢玩一点捉迷藏。
I like a little bit of hide and seek.
-这是我们的城市。-没人能躲得过我们。
- This is our city. - No one can hide from us here.
这是我们的城市。没人能躲得过我们。
This is our city. No one can hide from us here.
天啊，真厉害！
Jesus, that's strong!
她的?
That her?
对，就是她。
Yeah, that's her.
我不记得有人提醒过她是超模。
I don't recall getting a memo she was a supermodel.
Engleski吗?是吗?
Engleski? Yeah?
你做过保安？
You've worked security?
除此之外。
Among other things.
你们是怎么认识的？
How'd you guys meet?
监狱。
Prison.
实际上是同性恋游轮。
Gay cruise actually.
万宝路牛仔。
Marlboro Man.
他是个警察。
He was a cop.
我们也是。
So were we.
-有各种各样的警察。-他们不是我们。
-There are all kinds of cops. -They are not us.
-是的。-但我是说，这就是为什么我让他们帮我们做事。
- Yeah. -  But I mean, that's why I let them do the work for us.
我演警察跟演其他人一样。
I play the cops like I play everyone else.
开车就行了。
Just drive the car.
-现在他是我们打开金库的钥匙。-没有其他选择。
- Right now, he's our key to the vault. -  No other option.
金钱不是万能的。
Money flies no flag.
今晚邀请他。
Invite him tonight.
我们把他关进一个深洞，看他能不能爬出来。
We'll put him in a deep hole and see if he crawls out.
-好吗？-好吧。
- All right? - All right.
,你好。
--Bonjour.
听着，我们已经讨论过了。
Listen, we've already discussed this.
太累了，我们以后再谈。
This is exhausting, let's talk later.
——对不起。-他们越富有，骗子就越大。混蛋。
- Sorry. - The wealthier they are, the bigger the crook. Asshole.
一旦你成为贪婪的奴隶，你就完蛋了。
Once you become a slave to greed, you're fucked.
那我想我们都完蛋了。
Then I guess we are both fucked.
我能帮你什么忙吗？
So, how can I help you?
我想知道我能不能在你们的保险箱里租几个星期。
I was wondering if I can rent space in one of your vault boxes for a few weeks.
我有一些存货要进，我…我不喜欢把它放在办公室里。
I have some inventory coming in and I... I do not like the idea of keeping it in the office.
到底有多大的空间？
How much space exactly?
大约3000克拉。
Around 3,000 karats.
分摊每月的费用，我们就能做到。
Split the monthly cost and we can do it.
完美的。
Perfect.
好。
Bon.
他在这里。
He's here.
-你还好吗？-我很好，你呢？
- You good? - I'm good, you?
给他看。
Show him.
把它给我。
Give it to me.
我该怎么做？
What do I do with this?
横着拿，轻敲屏幕。
Hold it sideways, tap the screen.
就是那个拿着GPS信标的人吗？
That's the guy who had the GPS beacon?
This the guy who had the GPS beacon?
这是他。
That's him.
发短信给我。
Text it to me.
发短信给我们。
Text it to us.
——好的。-干得好。
- Okay. - Good job.
纯粹的狗屎。
Pure shit.
——哟!——嘿!
- Yo! - Hey!
你看起来不错。
You look good.
天呐。
Holy shit.
对吧?
Right?
这些是你的新女友吗？
So, these your new girlfriends?
别紧张，伙计。我们不着急。
Take it easy, man. We're in no rush.
尼克。-Slavko。
-Nick. -Slavko.
酷的名字。快乐。
Cool name. Pleasure.
德拉甘。尼克。
-Dragan. -Nick.
我了解你。
I know you.
尼克。
Nick.
慢慢来，兄弟。
Take your time, bro.
马克。
-Marko.
马可。
Marko.
——尼克。-去你妈的。
- Nicko. - Go fuck yourself.
够了!
Enough!
请坐。
Have a seat.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
那个游戏叫什么名字？
Hey, what's the name of that game?
就是你扔的那些小金属球？
You know, with the little metal balls that you throw?
——室外地滚球戏。——室外地滚球戏。
- Bocce. - Bocce.
你知道，今天在咖啡馆。我看到你们了。
You know, at the cafe today. I saw you guys there.
你的警校教得很好，尼克。
Your police academy taught you well, Nicko.
去他妈的警察。
Fuck the police.
是啊，去他妈的警察。
Yeah, fuck the police.
-那是什么？-Sljivo。
-What is that? -Sljivo.
自称吗?-Sljivo。Sljivovica。
-Say again? -Sljivo. Sljivovica.
当你没油的时候，你可以把这个放在你的车里。
When you run out of gas, you can put this in your car.
真恶心。
That's some nasty shit.
-这是什么？试试它吧。
-What is it? -Try it.
警察不吸毒。
Cops don't do drugs.
所以，帮你自己一个忙。
So, do yourself a favor.
别像个娘们儿。然后打那坨屎。
Stop being a pussy. And hit that shit.
天呐。
Holy shit.
认真对待。我们…我们在抽什么？
Seriously. What are we... what are we smoking?
大麻。
Hashish.
加上一点仙尘。
With a little pixie dust.
Pixie,什么?
Pixie, what?
你从来没试过吗？
E. You never try E?
是的，当然。
Yeah, of course.
好吧。
Okay.
我真他妈希望我能跳舞！
I wish I could fucking dance!
该死的欧洲规则！
Fuckin' Europe rules!
伙计，抱歉在90年代把你们炸得屁滚尿流。
Hey, man, sorry about bombing the shit out of you guys in the '90s.
现在,……那太糟了。
Now, that... that was fucked up.
他们杀了我母亲。
They killed my mother.
不,严重吗?
No, seriously?
我们去加入西方，但是西方不想要我们。
We went to join the West, but the West didn't want us.
所以，我们抢劫它。
So, we rob it.
我他妈的爱死你们了。
I fucking love you guys.
他妈的北约!他妈的北约!
-Fuck NATO! -Fuck NATO!
他妈的北约!他妈的他们!
-Fuck NATO! -Fuck 'em!
是的，是的，去他的北约！
Yeah, yeah, fuck NATO!
哦，我有一个。
Oh, I got one coming up.
他搞砸了。
He's fucked up.
嘿。不好的。去找尼克。走,走。
Hey. Not good. Go to Nicko. Go, go.
你知道我爱你。
You know I love you.
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
这是马科的前男友，他喝醉了。
This is Marko's ex, man, and he's trippin'.
稍微慢一点，好吗？
Just slow it down a little bit, all right?
-我告诉他了。-是的。
- I told him. - Yeah.
嘿，你他妈在干什么？
Hey, what the fuck are you doing?
嘿，嘿，嘿。嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
去他妈的。
Fuck this shit.
-嘿。-嘿。
-Hey. -Hey.
把你的手拿开。
Get your fucking hands off me.
-该死的戏剧女王。-走吧。
- Fucking drama queen. - Let's go.
嘿,嘿!
Hey, hey!
滚蛋!
Fuck off!
寒冷,寒冷。
Chill, chill.
搞什么鬼？
What the fuck?
-好吧，好吧，好吧——好的。
- Okay, okay, okay. - Okay.
你这个肮脏的混蛋！
You dirty motherfucker!
为什么，你想挨打吗？
Why, you wanna get smashed?
否。我不想被撞得稀巴烂。
No. I don't wanna get smashed.
嘿!嘿!
Hey! Hey!
啊!我们真的要现在谈这个吗？
Ah! We're really gonna do this right now?
草泥马!
Motherfucker!
哦,他妈的。狗屎,是的。
Oh, fuck. Shit, yeah.
是啊，美国硬汉。
Yeah, big American tough guy.
你在我们国家捣乱，是吧？
You start shit in our country, huh?
你以为我们是社会主义者吗？
You think we're socialist pussies over here, huh?
你他妈在玩什么把戏？
Yo, what the fuck are you playing at?
嘿。等等，等等，等等。我有一个。
Hey. Wait, wait, wait. I got one.
我现在真的会让你感到骄傲。
I'm really gonna make you proud right now.
——羊角面包。羊角面包。
- Croissant. Croissant.
-没问题。-你不喜欢？
- You got it. - You don't like it?
认为……他妈的!羊角面包。
Croiss... Fuck! Croissant.
这是狗屎!
It's shit!
来吧。
Come on.
我以为那是……我认为这很好。
I thought that was... I thought that was good.
唐尼!
Donnie!
-你他妈的支持我。
- You fucking had my back.
-哇，哇，哇！什么？-哇，哇，嘿。
-Whoa, whoa, whoa! What? -Whoa, whoa, hey.
-继续走。-好的，好的。
- Keep walking. - Okay, okay.
一直走。我们走吧。
Keep walking. Let's go.
我甚至都没叫优步！
I didn't even call an Uber!
他妈的……嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿！
Fucking... Hey, hey, hey, hey!
收割。快他妈的上车！
Get in... get in the fucking car!
-穆萨!-继续。动!
- Moussa! - Keep going. Move!
是的,是的。
Yes, yes.
让我们给他们一个教训。
Let's teach them a lesson.
几周前，有一架从非洲飞往安特卫普的航班。
A few weeks ago, there was a flight from Africa to Antwerp.
上面有东西。属于我们的东西。
It had something on it. Something that belongs to us.
致章鱼。
To the Octopus.
你偷走了它。
And you stole it.
把它拿回来。
Get it back.
——嘿!-给我滚回来！
- Hey! - Get the fuck back here!
你在开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding me?
你从黑手党那里偷钻石？
You stole diamonds from the fucking mafia?
就像我他妈的知道一样！
Like I fucking knew!
哦,他妈的!
Oh, fuck!
你要去哪里？尼克!尼克!
Where are you going? Nick! Nick!
把鞋脱了。你会沉。
Take your shoes off. You'll sink.
鞋。鞋。
Shoes. Shoes.
——现在,什么?
--Now, what?
你他妈怎么想的？游泳。
What the fuck do you think? Swim.
游泳吗?,尼克?
Swim? Where, Nick?
哦，去利比亚。
Oh, to Libya.
你他妈觉得呢，笨蛋？岸!
What the fuck do you think, dum-dum? To shore!
我游不了那么远。
I can't swim that fucking far.
我是负浮力。你不认识大卫·戈金斯吗？
I'm negatively buoyant. Don't you know David Goggins?
-别这么娘娘腔。操你!
-Don't be such a pussy. -Fuck you!
你觉得这附近有鲨鱼吗？
You think there are sharks around here?
实际上,是的。我想它被感染了。
Actually, yeah. I think it's infested.
你看起来有点像鲨鱼的食物。
You kind of look like shark food.
别跟我说话了。
Stop talking to me.
我恨你！
I hate you!
我他妈的也恨你。
I fucking hate you, too.
他妈的。我出去了。
Fuck it. I'm out.
哇，哇，哇！你是什么意思？
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What you mean?
我出去了。我的底线就在这里，管它叫什么鬼。
I'm out. Capo di tutti i capi or whatever the fuck it's called is where I draw the line.
他们的目标是家人。他们根本不在乎。
They go after families. They don't give a fuck.
你不能那样对我。
You can't do me like that.
好吧，你不这样我就死定了。
All right, I'm dead if you don't.
是你偷了那该死的钻石。我没有。
Well, you're the one that stole the fucking diamond. I didn't.
你要放我鸽子。你还不如逮捕我。
You gonna bail on me. You might as well arrest me.
他妈的。
Fuck it.
别他妈的跟着我。
Don't fucking follow me.
你跟踪我到这里。
You followed me here.
滚出去，贱人。
Dip out there, bitch.
宿醉还好吗，小姐？
How's the hangover, mademoiselle?
你在看吗?
You watching?
是的。
Yep.
大多数警卫什么都不做。
Most guards don't do shit.
抽烟，玩手机，看黄片。
Smoke, dick around on phones, watch porn.
-那些男孩不一样。-非常。
-Those boys are different. -Very.
这几个星期我一直在跟踪那些家伙。那些狗会打猎。
Been clocking those dudes for weeks. Those dogs can hunt.
是的。
Yeah.
这会很有趣的。
This is gonna be interesting.
你感觉到了吗？
You feeling it?
是的，我感觉到了。
Yeah, I'm feeling it.
警察变成了黑帮。
And the cop goes gangster.
给我滚过来，伙计。你的浓缩咖啡要凉了。
Get your ass over here, man. Your espresso's getting cold.
无防火门、无紧急出口、无出口点。
The WDC has no fire doors, no emergency exit, or egress point.
只有一扇门。一条路进去，一条路出去。
There's only one door. One way in, one way out.
在这个区域内的任何活动都会导致你被拍到一张照片。
Any movements within the district will result in you coming in a picture.
所以只有一个地方他们没在找。
So, there's only one place they're not looking.
向上。
Up.
布拉沃。德拉甘。
Bravo. Dragan.
你得把这个穿上。
You're gonna have to put this on.
这些是打折的吗？
These on sale or something?
我的两个男朋友呢？
Where are my two boyfriends?
他们出去了。
They're out.
受欢迎的。
Welcome.
Marko和Vuk回家了。你现在是黑豹了。
Marko and Vuk went home. You're a Panther now.
这是整个剧院。
This is the entire theater.
我们检查了这个地区的所有安保措施。
We've recce'd every security measure in the district.
如你所见，没有死区。
As you can see, there are no dead zones.
所以，我们需要创建一个。
So, we'll have to create one.
这个售货亭里有127个摄像头接入中央安保系统。
There are 127 cameras fed into central security right here in this kiosk.
他们只装了十个监控摄像头。
They only run ten CCTV monitors.
这127个视频每隔10秒循环一次。
So, those 127 feeds cycle through at ten-second intervals.
在任何给定的时间，其中117个视图是黑暗的。
At any given time, 117 of those views are dark.
我们将执行一次定时下降，这样我们就能在不被发现的情况下通过闭路电视监控的黑暗区域。
We will perform a timed descent that will move us undetected through those dark zones as a result of the CCTV monitoring cycle.
摄像头下线后的录像怎么办？
What about the recorded footage once the cameras are offline?
WDC的隐私法禁止这样做。
There's a WDC privacy law that prevents it.
所以没有录像。
So, no footage is being recorded.
它只是被实时观看。
It's just being viewed in real time.
但我们有一个盲点和一个问题。
But we have a blind spot and a problem.
所以只有门房，持证人，和他们的私人保安才有资格进入金库他们一定是执法人员。
So the only individuals that are granted access to the vault is the Concierge, the sightholders, and their private security who must be law enforcement.
我们试着出卖一些有权限的内部资产，但是…所以，你是我们的切入点。
We tried to flip some internal assets with access, but... So, you're our way in.
好吧。
Okay.
这是什么时候发生的？
When does this happen?
现在。
Right now.
就他妈现在。
Like, right the fuck now.
一切都好吗？
Everything all right?
否。
No.
奥布莱恩先生和我共事多年。
Mr. O'Brien has worked with me for years.
我给你洛杉矶治安官办公室的管理员发了邮件想要你的诚意，但没收到任何回复。
I emailed admin at your L.A. sheriff's office for your bona fides, but didn't receive anything.
你是说…你确定没收错邮件吗？
You mean, uh... You sure you got the right email?
也许……也许检查。
Maybe... maybe check.
-是的。-我不明白。
- Yeah. - I don't understand.
哦!
Oh!
我们到了。它去了我的垃圾。
Here we are. It went to my junk.
-抱歉。-这种事时有发生。
- Sorry for that. - It happens.
一切都很好。
Everything is okay.
-是的。美妙
-Yeah. Mm. -Wonderful.
好吧,男人。她在来的路上了。
Okay, man. She's on her way.
就站在这里？
Just stand here?
是的。
Yeah.
你好。——啊,你好。
-Bonjour. -Ah, bonjour.
这是尼克，我的安全主管。
This is Nick, my head of security.
尼克。Chava要求。
Nick. Chava Falcone.
你好。你好。
-Bonjour. -Bonjour.
-没有法语，是吧？
- Ah, no français,huh?
顺便说一下，德比。Nice-Monaco。你要去吗？
By the way, the derby. Nice-Monaco. Are you going?
——礼宾部的奥利维尔。-是的。
-Olivier, the Concierge. -Yeah.
我，一些朋友。我们要去支持者酒吧。
Me, some friends. We're going to a supporters' bar.
——周六?——是的。
- Saturday? - Yes.
-我可以和你一起去。-是的,你来。跟我们来吧。
-I might join you. -Yeah, come. Come with us.
谢谢。
Merci.
尼克会和你一起去存放存货。
So, Nick will go with you to deposit the inventory.
明天还行吗？
Does tomorrow still work?
是的。但明早第一件事是8点，因为我明天很忙。
Yeah. But first thing in the morning, eight o'clock, because I'm slammed tomorrow.
——确定。-谢谢。
- Sure. - Thank you.
见到你。
See you.
♬让你对我产生误解
♪ To get the wrong idea about me ♪
♬我没有什么好隐瞒的
♪ I don't have nothing to hide ♪
为什么,兄弟?为什么?
Why, bro? Why?
♬我想让全世界都知道我是个流氓
♪ I want the world to see I'm a gangsta ♪
♬黑帮黑鬼们♬跳起舞来吧
♪ Gangsta niggas ♪ Do your dance ♪
♬黑帮婊们挥手吧
♪ Gangsta bitches wave your hands ♪
♬看我，我在乎我的钱，我在乎我的纸，我在乎我的钱
♪ See me, I'm about my money My paper I'm about my dollars ♪
♬用这台mac和这台slack弹出衣领
♪ Popping collars with this mac and this slack ♪
嘿!
Hey!
为了真正的歹徒。
For real gangster.
说话客气点。
You watch your mouth.
他妈的!
Fuck!
所以你才一直这么兴奋。
This is why y'all so amped up all the time.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
嘿!
Hey!
——这就是音乐。
--Now, this is music.
好吧。
Okay.
哇。
Wow.
Romantico。
Romantico.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
你在耍我吗？
Are you fucking with me?
你应该多做爱，兄弟。
You gotta make love more often, bro.
看，德拉甘，他很熟练。
See, Dragan, he's smooth with it.
这副眼镜骗不了我。我看见你了！
Them glasses don't fool me. I see you!
是啊!兄弟，你憋住了。
Yeah! Bro, you pent up.
你的西装。这是ISR。记录在各个方向。
Your suit. It's an ISR. Records in every direction.
哦。好吧。
Oh. All right.
你确定这东西能行吗？
Sure this thing's gonna work?
我在500家珠宝店戴过了。他们的工作。
I've worn these in 500 jewelry stores. They work.
好吧，你是个女人。
Well, you're a woman.
她们一般不会被搜身，尤其是漂亮的。
They tend not to get frisked, especially beautiful ones.
警察也不会，尤其是好警察。
Well, neither do cops, especially good ones.
我他妈讨厌西装。
I fuckin' hate suits.
穿西装永远不会有好事发生。
Nothing good ever happens in a suit.
那天晚上真好玩。
That was fun the other night.
你知道，在俱乐部。
You know, at the club.
是的。良好的DJ。酷的战斗。
Yeah. Good DJ. Cool fight.
我刚离婚。
I just got divorced.
哦，那太可悲了。
Oh, that's so sad.
郑重声明，我对你没有吸引力。
And for the record, I have no attraction to you.
好吧。你有孩子吗？
Okay. You got any kids?
否。
No.
实际上,是的。
Actually, yeah.
你知道，我更喜欢诚实而不是胡扯。
You know, I prefer honesty rather than bullshit.
哦。
Oh.
那么，是的，我知道。我得到了……我有两个。
Then, yeah, I do. I got... I got two.
该死的!
Damn!
我还以为你要娶我呢。
I thought you were gonna wife me up.
我可以改一下答案吗？
Can I change my answer?
别搞砸了。
Don't fuck this up.
别耍我。
And don't fuck me over.
来吧。来吧。
Come on. Come on.
-你好。-你好。
- Bonjour. - Bonjour.
我的细节。
My detail.
我们在交易所和法尔科内小姐和礼宾部有个约会。
We have an appointment at the Bourse with Miss Falcone and the Concierge.
好吧。
All right.
请鉴定。
Identification, please.
谢谢。
Merci.
他们不会检查安检。
They won't pat down security.
你可以走了。
You're good to go.
凸轮。凸轮。
-Cam there. -Cam.
好吧。珍贵的货物。
Okay. Precious cargo.
非常感谢你，哈瓦。
Thank you so much, Chava.
我得去参加欢迎派对了。来了。
I have to go welcome parties. Come.
-你好。-你好。
- Bonjour. - Bonjour.
早上好。
Good morning.
早....。
Morning.
请。
Please.
礼宾部全天候管理保险库，住在七楼，每次预约都要陪同，每晚都要锁门。
The Concierge operates the vault 24/7, lives on the seventh floor, escorts every appointment, locks up every night.
把这些东西搬到任何地方——离那里很近……-非常危险。
Moving all this with him anywhere - near there would be... - very risky.
是的。但我们会根据他的动作来计时。
Yeah. But we'll just time it with his movements.
所以你不再当警长了？
So, no more being sheriff for you?
我容易伤害别人的感情。
I tend to hurt people's feelings.
这样你就能适应了。
Then you'll fit right in.
嗯。
Huh.
请。
Please.
-有一个热运动。-是的。
-There's a thermal motion. -Yeah.
-你能转过身吗？-对不起。
- Can you turn around? - I'm sorry.
这是保险库。艾蒙。
There is the vault. Armon.
请把公文包放在桌子上。
You can put the briefcase on the desk, please.
确定。
Sure.
奥利维尔，你星期六来看比赛吗？
Are you coming to the game Saturday, Olivier?
当然!我都等不及了！
Of course! I can't wait!
-我给我们订了张桌子。完美的!
-I got us a table. -Perfect!
给你。
Here you go.
剩下的问题是从走廊到门厅的监控摄像头，太高了，我们无法覆盖。
The remaining issue is that the security camera from hallway to the foyer, is too high up for us to cover.
这是唯一一个不循环的相机。
And that's the only camera that doesn't cycle.
如果我们掩护自己呢？
What if we cover ourselves?
量子隐形?
Quantum Stealth?
我们得用手指操那个技术。
We need to finger fuck that tech.
嗯。
Huh.
我们在看什么？
What we looking at?
我看到了石头。
I saw the stone.
啊哈。
Uh-huh.
左上角。
Top left side.
第二排，倒数第五。
Second row, fifth from the top.
我看见那该死的石头了。
I saw the fucking stone.
艾伦，达科，这是武克。
Allen, Darko, this is Vuk.
武克，这些是猛虎。
Vuk, these are the Tigers.
好。
Good.
低科技打败了高科技。
Low tech beats high tech.
立即观看。
Watch now.
瞧!
Voila!
他妈的。
Fuck.
我不习惯这里的大蒜。
Not used to all the garlic over here.
现在，你知道，转过身来。
Now, you know, turn around.
我猜他在做销售。
I guess he's making some sales.
哦，这是冰淇淋吗？
Oh, is this ice cream?
什么？
What?
冰淇淋。
Gelato.
太他妈好了。
It's fucking good.
——嗯。
- Mm-hmm.
这是热的吗？
Yo, is that thermal?
——嗯?——是……这是热的吗？
- Huh? - Is... Is that thermal?
-是的。
- Yeah.
都做了什么?都锁好了吗？
All done? Everything locked up?
是。
Yes.
好了。享受比赛吧。
Great. Enjoy the match.
你会赢的。我们走吧!
You're in for a win. Let's go!
是的。
Oui.
礼宾部刚走。
Concierge just left.
在出口见你开着货车。
See you with the van at egress point.
-祝你好运。-收到。
- Good luck. - Copy.
…盔甲穿刺。
...armour piercing.
每第五轮。给你。
Every fifth round. Here you go.
-你是说总共50个？-50年,是的。
-Are you saying 50, total? -50, yes.
摩纳哥1 - 0。
Monaco 1-0.
那是越位！为什么?
That was offside! Why?
太烦人了，橄榄球更好！
It's so annoying, rugby's better!
每一次。看起来……
Every time. Look...
胡迪尼一号，我是实际碳。
Houdini One, this is Carbon Actual.
市场沟通部检查。
Comms check.
实际碳，收到。
Carbon Actual, copy.
审稿清晰。
Comms clear.
胡迪尼一号继续前进。
Houdini One moving on theater.
收到。
Copy that.
胡迪尼一号在剧院。
Houdini One in theater.
好了!
Nice!
我们扯平了。我们又回到了游戏中。
We're even. We're back in the game.
来吧，伙计们。
Come on guys.
胡迪尼一号，你在阿姆斯特尔。
Houdini One, you are red at Amstel.
还有20秒绿灯。
Twenty seconds to green light.
收到，碳素实物。
Copy, Carbon Actual.
等待绿色信号。
Standing by for green.
还有10秒绿灯。
Ten seconds to green light.
五、四……
Five, four...
你是绿色的。格林到贝克。
You're green. Green to Becks.
绿色的。
Green.
收到，你在贝克街红了。红在贝克。
Copy, you're red at Becks. Red at Becks.
离绿灯还有12秒。站在。
Twelve seconds to green light. Stand by.
胡迪尼一号，盯住小贝。
Houdini One, holding at Becks.
五，四，三……
Five, four, three...
天啊，太深奥了。
Jesus, that's deep.
是的。
Yeah.
他妈的下地狱。
Fuckin' hell.
还有80秒就红了。
Eighty seconds to red.
收到，碳素公司。
Copy that, Carbon Actual.
嗯。
Hmm.
距离红色还有60秒。
Sixty seconds to red.
来吧。
Come on.
离红色还有40秒。
Forty seconds to red.
还有20秒就红了。
Twenty seconds to red.
还有十秒就红了。
Ten seconds to red.
五，四，三，二，一。
Five, four, three, two, one.
电晕是红色的。红色在科罗娜。
Corona's red. Red at Corona.
胡迪尼一号，定位。
Houdini One, location.
钻石矿井里的胡迪尼一号。
Houdini One in Mineshaft at Diamond.
胡迪尼一号，量子在钻石。
Houdini One, Quantum at Diamond.
量子在钻石。
Quantum at Diamond.
拜托，伙计们，就一个！
Come on guys, just one!
-我操。-披着斗篷的胡迪尼。
- Holy shit. - Houdini in the mantle.
收到。
Copy.
-不在这里。-他妈的不在这里！
- It's not here. - It's not fucking here!
你什么意思，他妈的不在这儿？
What do you mean, it's not fucking here?
好吧，继续，继续。
Okay, just keep goin', keep goin'.
——请把这个关掉！不见了!
--Please, turn this off! Gone!
——操!-也不在这里
- Fuck! - It's not here either.
加油！加油。
Come on, come on.
-你在干什么？
- What are you doing?
不!不要去。什么？
No! Don't go. What?
我很抱歉。再见,伙计们。
I'm sorry. Bye, guys.
他妈的!
Fuck!
胡迪尼一号，管家回来了。
Houdini One, Housekeeper is home.
返回矿井。
Return to Mineshaft.
那是什么？
Actual, what's that?
-管家回来了-给我滚出去！
- Housekeeper is home. - Get the fuck out now!
他妈的!我们得走了，得走了！
Fuck! We gotta go, we gotta go!
-你看到了吗？——没有。
- You see it? - No.
该死，它在哪儿？
Shit, where is it?
比赛怎么样？
How about the match?
令人难以置信的。
-Unbelievable.
一次机会，一个目标。没有辩护。
Once chance, one goal. And no defense.
这里的。这里的。
It's here. It's here.
-我们得走了，唐尼。-不不不
- We gotta go, Donnie. - No, no, no.
-等等。-我们得走了。
- Hold on. - We gotta go.
在这。
It's here.
-来吧。-来吧。来吧。
- Come on. - Come on. Come on.
再等一下。
One more sec.
唐尼，起来。
Donnie, get up.
-拜托！来吧!——等等!
- Come on! Come on! - Wait!
我们需要一个新教练。
We need a new coach.
-那太贵了。-对。
-That will be expensive. -Right.
-我会锁门的。你可以回家了。
-I'll lock up. You can go home.
明天见。-祝你晚上愉快。
See you tomorrow. -Have a nice evening.
多尼，别管了。
Donnie, just fucking leave it.
我们得走了！
We gotta go now!
-天啊，等等。-快起来！
- Jeez, hold on. - Just get up!
——等等!——等等!等等!等等!
- Wait! - Wait! Wait! Wait!
等等!
Wait!
谢天谢地。
Thank fucking God.
胡迪尼一号，请回答。
Houdini One, come in.
胡迪尼一号正在上矿井。
Houdini One moving up Mineshaft.
收到。
Copy.
胡迪尼一号在科罗娜。
Houdini One holding at Corona.
你是科罗娜的新手。
You're green at Corona.
140秒后到达科罗娜。
140 seconds green at Corona.
袋子是安全的。
Bags are secure.
在科罗娜还有60秒。
Sixty seconds at Corona.
在的日子!在的日子!
At Becks! At Becks!
-等一下贝克。科罗娜红色，45分钟。
- Hold at Becks. - Corona red in 45.
科罗娜红色，30秒。
Corona red in 30.
他妈的。
Fuck.
在贝克等一等。科罗娜红色，20分钟后。
Hold at Becks. Corona red in 20.
小贝红色。
Becks red.
三秒内切换路线。等待命令。
Three seconds to switch route. Hold for command.
小贝绿色。小贝绿色。
Becks green. Becks green.
碳实际，我们很清楚。
Carbon Actual, we are clear.
好吧。
Okay.
我们该怎么办呢。
What are we gonna do about this.
看看这些笨蛋。
Look at these dumbasses.
哦,他妈的。
Oh, fuck.
狗屎!
Shit!
——尼克!尼克!
--Nick! Nick!
监控14。
Monitor 14.
那是什么鬼东西？
What the hell is that?
嘿!那是什么鬼东西？
Hey! what the hell is that?
不知道。
No idea.
你觉得是从屋顶传来的吗？
Think it's coming from the roof?
我不知道。
I don't know.
搞什么鬼……我们得守住屋顶。
What the f... We need to secure the roof.
-走，走，走吧。-来吧。
- Go, go, come on. - Come on.
来吧。
Come on.
我去查一下。
I'll check it out.
胡迪尼一号，警犬追踪。消失。
Houdini One, dogs on the scent. Vanish.
——操!-走，走，走。
- Fuck! - Go, go, go.
-来吧。-来吧，尼克。
- Come on. - Come on, Nick.
-没问题。
- You got it.
是的。
Yeah.
-把背包扔了。-妈的！
- Throw the backpack. - Oh, fuck!
好的,走吧。走,走。
Okay, go. Go, go.
极!极!
The pole! The pole!
移动，移动，移动。动!
Move, move, move. Move!
真实的碳，贝克汉姆是绿色的吗？
Carbon Actual, is Becks green?
收到。确认胡迪尼一号，贝克绿。
Copy. Confirm Houdini One, Becks green.
收到。封锁大门，限制人员活动，直到我们清理完毕。
Copy. Lock down the gates and restrict personnel movement until we clear this.
有东西从屋顶上掉下来了。-什么?
-Something fell off the roof. -What?
我会清理屋顶，然后往下走。你在二楼巡逻，从楼梯间走。在中间会合。
I'll clear the roof, then move down. You patrol level 2 up, take the stairwells. Meet in the middle.
我要你离开中庭楼梯，好吗？
So, I want you to clear the atrium stairs, all right?
好了,好了。
Okay, great.
别忘了把电梯锁上，好吗？
And don't forget to lock down the fucking elevator, yeah?
明白了。
Got it.
屋顶清晰。
Roof clear.
碳素一号，我需要胡迪尼一号的位置。
Carbon Actual, I need the location of Houdini One.
胡迪尼一号的位置。
Location of Houdini One.
5清除到4。
5 cleared moving to 4.
搞什么鬼？
What the fuck?
-别碰武器。-放松点。
- Hands off weapon. - Just relax.
别傻了。好吧?
Don't be stupid. All right?
你他妈是谁？！
Who the fuck are you?!
别犯傻了。
Don't be fucking stupid.
搞什么鬼？搞什么鬼？
What the fuck? What the fuck?
投火!开火!
Shots fire! Shots fired!
照片被解雇了!开火!——操吗?
-Shots fired! Shots fired! -The fuck?
触发报警。
Trigger alarm.
搞什么鬼？
What the fuck?
放松,放松。我瞄准了质心。
Relax, relax. I aimed center mass.
你是好的。好吧?
You're okay. All right?
不过会疼上几天。
It's gonna hurt a few days, though.
很抱歉。
Sorry about that.
陌生人。消失。该。现在，现在，现在！
Stranger. Vanish. Northside. Now, now, now!
-我们抓到他了。-我们抓到他了。
- We got him. - We got him.
该。该。
Northside. Northside.
收到。
Copy that.
是他!是他!
It's him! It's him!
-快走，快走！-我们得走了！
- Let's go, let's go! - We gotta go!
啊,操!
Ah, fuck!
又是该死的保时捷！
The fucking Porsche again!
不错的WDC 14。
TRC Nice for WDC 14.
白色保时捷轿车，车牌号码…搞什么鬼？
Porsche sedan, white, Plate number... What the fuck?
草。ANPR。
Shit. ANPR.
-抓住那个盘子。—运行。
- Grab that plate there. - Run it.
上面写了什么？
What does it say?
重复一遍，白色保时捷。
I repeat, white Porsche.
白色保时捷向东行驶在罗伯特街400号。
White Porsche heading east on 400 block of Rue de Robert.
如果我们中有人受伤，斯洛博丹会把你的那份拿走。
If any of us get burned, Slobodan will put your cut away.
当你出来的时候，它会等着你。祝你好运。
And it'll be waiting for you when you get out. Good luck.
的焦点。
Focus.
祝你好运，兄弟。
Good luck, brother.
他妈的。这是不可能的。
Fuck. It's not possible.
他妈的。-你他妈在开玩笑吧。
-Fuck. -Are you fucking kidding me.
闪光灯,闪光灯。我们被抢劫了。
Flash, flash. We've been robbed.
重复一遍，我们被抢劫了。
I repeat, we have been robbed.
注意六点钟方向。
Watch our six.
那不是警灯。
Those aren't police headlights.
他们也不友好。
They're not friendly either.
他妈的。
Fuck.
玛格。
Mag.
开车。我开枪。大声喊，刹车。
Drive. I shoot. Call out, brakes.
收到。
Copy.
草。他们有两个。
Shit. There's two of them.
-天啊！——操!
- Oh, God! - Fuck!
拿着方向盘！轮!
Take the wheel! Wheel!
——嘿!动!动!-我很好！我很好!
- Hey! Move! Move! - I'm good! I'm good!
玛格变化。
Mag change.
我需要更好的镜头。
I need a better shot.
-等等！我听不见你说什么。——刹车!
- Hold on! I can't hear you. - Brake!
他妈的!我他妈喝醉了，伙计！
Fuck! I'm fucking hit up, man!
坚持下去!
Hold on!
杂志的变化。-你还好吧？
-Mags change. -You all right?
是的，我没事。
Yeah, I'm okay.
我们正在改变杂志！
We're changing mag!
准备好了!
Ready again!
我们走吧!
Let's go!
该死，还在我们这边。
Shit, still on us.
-你能解开吗？-他妈的努力。
- Can you loose 'em? - Fucking trying.
-那些家伙是司机。-该死。
- Those dudes are drivers. - Oh, shit.
右车道伙计，保持右车道！
The right lane man, keep the right lane!
狗屎!他妈的!
Shit! Fuck!
在这一边。我瞄得很准。
Right this side. I got a clean shot.
抓到你了，break。
Got you, break.
我出去了。玛格变化。
I'm out. Mag change.
我有弹药。
I've got ammo.
现在!现在!现在!
Now! Now! Now!
他妈的。
Fuck this.
他妈的,是啊!
Fuck, yeah!
草泥马!
Motherfucker!
打它!打它!
Hit it! Hit it!
好吧，我退出。
Okay, I'm out.
他妈的!
Fuck!
那是什么鬼东西？
What the fuck was that?
他的错。
His fault.
-就这样？
- That's it?
-早上好。-早上好。
- Good morning. - Good morning.
这里。
This way.
我丈夫在楼上。
My husband is upstairs.
马里奥!我们在这里。
Mario! We're here.
他们已经来了。
They've arrived.
-嘿，嘿！-嗨。
- Hey, hey! - Hey.
-嘿,你。-嘿。
-Hey, you. -Hey.
-你没事吧？-是啊，伙计。
- You okay? - Yeah, man.
-斯洛。——雅克。
- Slobodan. - Jean-Jacques.
-很高兴认识你。-很高兴认识你。
-Nice to meet you. -Nice to meet you.
斯洛博丹，他是尼克。
Slobodan, he is Nick.
和我们坐下来。
Sit down with us.
请坐。
Take a seat, please.
啊!
Ah!
是啊!
Yeah!
谢谢你！
Thank you.
——谢谢。-不客气。
- Thanks. - You're welcome.
先生。
Signore.
-谢谢。-谢谢。
- Thank you. - Thank you.
啊。你拯救了小镇。
Ah. You saved the town.
嗯?-好的,伙计们。请站起来。
-Huh? -Okay, guys. Stand up, please.
敬世纪大盗。
To heist of century.
还有黑豹党。
And to the Panthers.
啊!
Ah!
-你还好吗？-我很好。
- You good? - I'm good.
哦，来吧。
Oh, come on.
-看啊。——不!
- Look at that. - No!
我们给你留了这个。
We saved this one, we saved this one for you.
-谢谢。谢谢你！你的风格。
-Thank you. Thank you. -Your style.
嘿。把手拿开，伙计。
Hey. Keep your hands to yourself, man.
嘿，嘿，嘿！嘿!
Hey, hey, hey! Hey!
——嘿!——别动!
- Hey! - Freeze!
别动!警察!
-Freeze! -Police!
——好吧,好吧!
--Okay, okay!
不要动!
Don't move!
嘿，嘿，嘿！
Hey, hey, hey!
别动，别动！
Don't move, don't move!
不要动!手回来了!
Don't move! Hands back!
我们走吧!我们走吧!
Let's go! Let's go!
嘿!嘿!
Hey! Hey!
走吧!走吧!
Go! Go!
动,动!
Move, move!
动!
Move!
我们走吧!
Let's go!
你没事吧?
You okay?
是的。
Yeah.
你愿意来帮我吗？
You want to do the honors?
你去做吧。你的管辖范围内。
You do it. Your jurisdiction.
你所说的一切都将成为呈堂证供。
Anything you say can and will be used against you in the court of law.
你有权请律师
You have the right to an attorney...
考虑到这些权利，你想和我谈谈吗？
With these rights in mind, do you wish to speak to me?
好打。
Well played.
我猜。
I guess.
你还要点别的吗？
Do you want something else?
我要一个羊角面包。
I'll have a croissant.
冻糕。
Parfait.
你知道，你进来是对的，对吧？
You know, you did the right thing coming in, huh?
很奇怪，对吧？
It's strange, huh?
生活在另一边感觉很好，不是吗？
Living on the other side feels good, no?
是的。
Yeah.
太好了。
Too good.
尊重。
Respect.
该回家了吧？
Time to go home, huh?
什么?
To what?
访客。手铐。
Visitor. Handcuffs.
快点。我没有一整天的时间。快来一个。
Hurry up. I haven't got all day. Come one, quickly.
坐下来。不要浪费时间。
Sit down. And no messing around.
你有五分钟时间。
You've got five minutes.
那很有趣。
That was fun.
我们扯平了？
So, we even?
是的。我们扯平了。
Yeah. We're even.
自我感觉良好？
Feel good about yourself?
事实上,没有。
Actually, no.
说实话，我以为我会感觉好一点。
I thought I would feel a little better, to be honest.
你就是一坨屎。
You're a piece of shit.
不过我确实救了你的命。
I did save your life, though.
那是真的吗？
So, that was real?
是的。
Yeah.
所以你一直都在耍我？
So, you've just been fuckin' with me this whole time?
否。否。不是一直都这样。
No. No. Not the whole time.
但说到底，老虎的斑纹是无法改变的。
But at the end of the day, a tiger just can't change his stripes.
只是不能。
Just can't.
再见，小姐。
I'll see you, Fraulein.
顺便说一下……靠左坐。
By the way... sit back left.
打解锁!手放在窗户上！
Hit unlock! Hands on the window!
左后!
Back left!
准备行动。
Get ready to move.
我们就这样了结了吗？
Do we just get this over with already?
他说我们应该快点结束这一切。
He's saying we should get this over with.
否。
No.
-嘿，各位。-给他拿点喝的。
- Hey, guys. - Get him something to drink.
要有礼貌。他是我们的客人。
Be polite. He's our guest.
嘿,男孩。怎么了?
Hey, boy. What's wrong?
Rilassare,安静的。
Rilassare, tranquillo.
他说：“放轻松。好好享受你的啤酒。”
He says, "Relax. Enjoy your beer."
他说如果他想让你走，那早就走了。
He says that if he wanted you gone, that would have happened a long time ago.
他想见见你。
He wants to meet you.
因为他想见见把他的东西拿回来的人。
Because he wanted to meet the man who got his goods back.
因为他想知道你是怎么做到的。
Because he wants to know how the hell you did it.
你他妈的就是哈利·胡迪尼！
You are Harry fucking Houdini!
现在，你为我工作。
And now, you work for me.
那么，下一步是什么？
So, what's next?
如果我是自己土地的国王
♪ If I was the king of my own land ♪
♪面对尘埃的风暴♪我会战斗到底♪
♪ Facing tempests of dust ♪ I'll fight until the end ♪
我梦中的生物，起来和我一起跳舞吧
♪ Creatures of my dreams, raise up and dance with me ♪
♬从现在到永远♬我是你的国王
♪ Now and forever ♪ I'm your king